Speaker 1: Casey's public service announcement for dudes in the car world. Be nice to girls in the car world. And
Speaker 2: Paul came up and said, awesome Maserati, it's Taylor and Casey.
Speaker 3: Man, this is sort of like Pride and Prejudice in the car world mixed with just like a touch of sexism. Interesting, but not cool.
KW makes the perfect
Speaker 4: suspension for every demand. Find them in the description below. What's up, people? Well, today I want to talk about an interesting experience
Speaker 2: I had this weekend and how I think it relates on the car community and the car world, especially how that relates to women who are car enthusiasts, car owners, etc. Now, you always say you got to walk a mile in a man's shoes. Well, you kind of got to walk a mile in a woman's shoes, which is way Any more difficult because they've got some funky heels.
Speaker 2: which i should probably hey comment below if you want to see me do a toe heel driving video in high heels i think that's ridiculous and interesting and we'd all learn something
Speaker 5: here but i digress so many of you know that my wife fairly recently bought her first exotic car she likes very much it's a 2008 maserati gran turismo it's white with a red interior and we recently i did the x-pipe for her she changed her own oil we got some neat wheels put them on and it's a wonderful car and she loves it she's really proud
of it so
This
Speaker 5: past weekend, we went down to Columbus, thought we'd get together with my old Cars and Coffee crew there, I went to Midwestern Auto Group where it was, real fun time, and we took her car. I didn't really wanna drive two cars at a time 'cause we were gonna do kinda weekend fun trip things, and her Maz is very comfortable to ride around in. And, you know, we'll share driving duties, things like that, but
I told
Speaker 5: her, I'm like, we're going to Cars and Coffee, it's your car, you're the one driving in, I do not wanna go in and get any credit for it 'cause people will
Speaker 5: think it's either my car or I'm the one just doing it and it's not her car of her enjoyment. So I wanted
Speaker 6: her to drive in and take credit for it, but she was being all bashful and didn't wanna do it because she's like, well, people are gonna be watching me when I have to back into space. I'm like, you're cool, it's the same as if there's
Speaker 7: nobody there, just it'll be fun, everybody'll
Speaker 8: love it. - Well guys, obviously a big thanks to Policy Genius because when it comes to insurance, it's nice to get it right. But
Speaker 9: more importantly than that, my wife Taylor and I have actually been using this company for the last two years before they were ever part of a sponsor from this channel. So I hope you'll give them the time of day
Speaker 9: Because on average, they're saving their clients $1,250 a year on their home and auto insurance. Basically, how it works is that Policy Genius works as a broker or a marketer. So they go out there, out to bat for you to compare all of the top brands, policy, insurance companies to find you the best rates, period. So
Speaker 10: guys, what you need to do, same thing I did. Oh no, because my wife is smart and told me what to do. And now I'm being smart and telling you what to do. So go to policygenius.com for
Speaker 10: KC, C-A-S-E-Y, very important,
Speaker 11: and check it out. They'll get started, get right on the team for you, know what you and your life is about for your home and auto insurance needs, and make that happen. So obviously guys, big savings coming up,
I love
Speaker 4: it. So I got her to do that and she was happy, and we're rolling in earlier, and the guy that runs it, Paul, was super
Speaker 5: nice, and he came up, and this was kind of a really nice moment for her as a car enthusiast, and
Speaker 2: just person. And Paul came up and said,
Speaker 2: "Awesome Maserati, it's Taylor and Casey." And it was just a little thing, but Paul said her name first, because her car, she's rolling in, she's the
Speaker 5: driver, and I'm just sitting in there riding B, you know what I mean? But that was cool, because I'm the longer term car guy, the more, you know, internet famous one or whatever, and I've gone to the cars and coffee for years and years, and everybody knows me,
but
Speaker 5: Taylor gets the credit. I thought that was really cool of Paul
Speaker 2: putting on that event and why I think that event's going to go a lot of people. But that's not really the case that I started to see out there in the normal public with car enthusiasts and such. So
Speaker 5: let me get into this. And by the way, I'm not gonna knock or dig on cars
and coffee. That
Speaker 3: car was totally cool. It's kind of just something that I perceived. And I'm like, man, this is sort of like pride and prejudice in the car world mixed with just like a touch of sexism. Interesting, but not cool.
so
Speaker 3: cars and coffee was cool we had fun people saw her car they liked it she
Speaker 2: got some people took pictures and tagged us in it whatever like they do but before we went down there you know obviously my wife would be out driving her car and stuff
Speaker 5: and typically when i drive one of my cars um whether somebody recognizes me from internet or they just see the car for the first time you know people be like nice car love it great that's cool looks you know thumbs up stuff like that with you see with car enthusiasts and actually something weird i noticed
Speaker 5: with my old white Porsche 944 with a martini sticker. It was really strange because I've had women come up to me and compliment that car, which is not normal for most cars. But, so my wife driving around, she would go to the grocery
Speaker 2: store or just out and about wherever it is, shopping, going to post office, something like that. And I asked her, do you ever get any compliments, people thumbs up and whatnot? And she actually said no.
Speaker 2: I usually have guys glaring at me when I get out. I'm like, are you sure about that? Like you're just thinking that 'cause you're kind of self-conscious 'cause you're driving a flashy car now? And she's like, no, they just kind of glare at me. And I'm like, all right. So I sort of paid attention to that. And she didn't mention
Speaker 5: that anybody complimented her car other than the neighbors or people we know are nice people, but just out there in general.
So when we were in
Speaker 5: Columbus where cars and coffee had a lot of fun and then we left and you know we're going to go out we're going to go to restaurants we're going to go shopping we're going to go you know do a couple things over a weekend right and regardless of where we went you'd hear people talking or people would say about the car and even one time we're in high street short north area walking around of Columbus kind of downtown and somebody else drove by in a white Maserati Gran Turismo different car and a bunch of people on the street you heard them say Maserati stuff like that. People do notice funny cars,
even if I
Speaker 5: don't think they do but when i was driving this happened once at the hotel we were staying at we got out and there were people there um and then another time in a motorcycle dealership parking lot and a couple of times just out and about wherever but so we get out of the car at the hotel it's later in the evening and we're getting out and there was like a whole family over there and they're like hey man nice car i like the maserati and the wheels
Speaker 3: And the first thing I said is,
Speaker 2: thanks, but it's her car. Because I am not about to take any credit for a car that's not mine, even though my wife's conning me into driving. I would rather ride. It's like, honey, drive your car. I'm trying to make you want to do this, so I don't have to drive. It's not gonna work.
But
Speaker 5: anyway, so I did that. And, but the guy kept talking to me. They, even though it was like a whole family and there were some women there, they didn't like direct the conversation, the compliments
to her.
They
Speaker 2: kept talking to me. It's like that's really cool. I like the wheels. I'm like yeah, man But like her car she changed the oil and everything and they never directed the conversation to her like her car it's kind
of like You
Speaker 2: know and we were just kind of walking because I'm not trying to draw attention
or
Speaker 5: anything But it sort of noticed that first but then the other thing I noticed was there was a number of times that weekend that some of you like hey, it's an awesome car. I'm like actually it's my wife's or it's her car, you know, etc. and
Not
Speaker 5: one of those times did the person say anything to her. Or even look at her, they just kinda looked at me and said it. And
Speaker 6: then, the one time we went to Iron Pony, which is an enormous motorcycle superstore, biggest one in the country of safety gear, riding gear, and bikes, and stuff like that, and service and all. And we're coming out,
and
Speaker 6: Maserati Gran Turismo is kind of a flashy luxury car, which isn't the norm in a motorcycle dealership parking lot. You're usually gonna get like, "Yeah, dudes." You know what I
Speaker 5: mean?
Not a
Speaker 5: fancy luxury car kind of in there, but you get all kinds, of course. And so we go to get in the car and there's this middle-aged
Speaker 3: gentleman walking by. Seemed kind of nice. Maybe came from the vintage bike races at Mid-Ohio. And he goes, "Maserati, all right. You don't see too many of those. Nice car." And he just enjoyed it as a genuine car enthusiast. It wasn't anything about the exotic world or flex.
And
Speaker 3: I'm like, well, thanks, man, but it's my wife's car. And she's like right there, right next to me looking. And he's like, yeah, I really like, and kept talking to me. And that's all right. But I was like, of
all the
Speaker 3: times people said something about the car,
Speaker 2: even when I was deflecting it, like, here you go, this person standing right here, this is her car, I'm going to go away now. They didn't even, like, not once direct the compliment to her or, like, try to give her a thumbs up. They just kept it at me or kept going with it. And...
Speaker 2: That was so bizarre to me because it's not
Speaker 3: my car, but it kind of dawned on me afterward, it's because I'm a guy. Cars and sports cars, exotic cars, motorcycles, etc. are classically a male-dominated world. That's very much a male thing to do. Let's be honest, this channel right now is a 97.5% sausage fest. Yes, or at least that's what the demographics say.
And
Speaker 5: that's just natural. That's kind of the way the car world is. I mean,
Speaker 6: it's kind of like engineering. Look, if you want to pick up chicks in college, don't go into mechanical engineering, okay? Go into like nursing or veterinarian school or something. You know what I mean? Like there's things that men like
Speaker 5: and there's things that women classically like. And we live in a funny time where, you know, like we don't want to admit that, but also we live in a funny time because we're also very entrenched in that and it's weird. But
Speaker 1: with this regard,
I think
Speaker 1: it's kind of important, and this is like Casey's public service announcement for dudes in the car world. Be nice to girls in car world, duh. If you've got like this kind of funny feeling because a woman has a car that you like or admire
Speaker 2: and want,
Speaker 2: don't immediately interpersonally hate on her or not want to engage that person in conversation about the car or not feel okay with paying a compliment to that person
Speaker 5: because
what
Speaker 5: you're thinking may not be true it's cool if women are into cars and I think we need to as men be a little less standoffish or prideful or having prejudice like you know like literally pride and prejudice of the cars world
I think
Speaker 5: we need to be a little more open and just cognizant of that, the fact that we're ingrained with this male-dominated thing. So just be cool. And yeah, you can judge for yourself, whether they're car people or not or whatever. But at least give that person the credit of potentially being a true car enthusiast and like it, and maybe somebody that you would enjoy engaging in conversation with. And I think that's just going to be more welcoming and more fun
um
Speaker 5: yeah it's something i didn't really realize because let's be honest there's not many women in the car world so we don't get that opportunity but it's something i think we should just think about we don't have to freak out but let's just be cool and look at ourselves and how we engage um to engage normal um that's easier said than done for men yes i'm well aware but um i did notice that uh i didn't really detract from my wife and she doesn't really like the attention anyway
Speaker 5: uh necessary but um it kind of made me a little sad for her because i hope that when she's out enjoying the car that she worked hard to be able to buy and then also has put in sweat acridy working on or building that she can enjoy it out in public just like any car guy or car gal can um and be fun um but haters gonna hate screw them
But
Speaker 5: anyway, just kind of want to bring that up, guys.
Just a
Speaker 5: little social thing, not a rant, not crying about something. It was just something I had a dude realization about that I think we should be cooler about. So that's it. Please
Speaker 3: subscribe below. Build's coming up, racing, crazy things, also tips, et cetera, driving tips, a lot of things. Also hit that bell because I think this is the best channel on YouTube. Actually, it's not. I recently found something called Thug Notes. Look it up.
Speaker 6: It's awesome. The dude talks about classic literature
in a
Speaker 6: very fun, relatable way.
but yeah
Speaker 13: you should totally subscribe to my channel too that's all i got uh it is a fun community of
Speaker 3: cars for men and women alike and i hope we're cool to everybody catch you later a huge thank you to crush proof tubing company since 1949 in macomb ohio
Speaker 14: they've been manufacturing custom rubber and plastic tubes for every industry imaginable no tooling or mold costs fasten free custom samples and american-made quality is what sets them apart but for me i'm most excited about their exhaust evacuation
Speaker 10: kit. Different modular pieces
Speaker 10: and their convoluted custom hoses make it so that i can adapt any car truck or motorcycle with an internal combustion engine to get those exhaust gases out of my shop so i can keep working in safety and comfort but beyond just that they build a variety of hoses for a custom oem world you'll see stretchable drain tubing and bellows as well as agriculture medical and military so again guys crush proof tubing company crushproof.com and go down in the description below to see where to get your free samples for industry or your exhaust tubing